

# Samet Sunman

50. Yil Mh. 2108. Sk. No:25 34265 - Sultangazi İstanbul/Turkey

sametsunman@yandex.com Portfolio: http://asnus.com/sametsunman\_ Github: http://github.com/sametsunman **Linkedin:** http://linkedin.com/in/sametsunman Phone: +90 (541) 577 91 66

**OBJECTIVE** 

My name is Samet Sunman and I am 23 years old. Technology have been in my life since I was a kid and I have always loved anything related with computer. I started to code and design at a very young age. Most of my skills and knowledge are selftaugh. I've studied Computer Engineering at Duzce University. During my study I was in Erasmus+ student exchange program at Lublin University of Technology in Poland for one semester. I have successfully completed all my courses and graduated. In the summer of 2017, I did my first internship at Boyner Büyük Mağazacılık A.Ş. in the information technology department as a software intern. In summer of 2018, I completed my second internship at General Mobile's mobile application development unit. Now I'm currently working at Ajans Press Group as a Software Developer since March 2019. I know C#, Java and Kotlin languages. Also I've expeirence in .NET Core and React.Js Frameworks.

E-mail:

WORK **EXPERIENCE** 

## **Ajans Press**

March 2019 — Present

Junior Software Developer

- Developed web pages for company personnels with ASP.NET
- Developed new project with .NET Core and React.JS

#### **General Mobile**

August 2018 — September 2018

Mobile Application Development Intern

- Learned Java and Kotlin Languages
- Developed Burn Dollars Game in Google Play
- Developed Movie Guide App with MovieDb API

## **Boyner**

August 2017 — September 2017

Software Development Intern

- Developed new Javascript modules developed for blog based Joomla
- Developed intelligence game with C# and Windows Forms
- Designed multiplayer game with .Net Framework, SignalR and Html

### **QUALIFICATIONS**

I specialize in Full Stack Development as my knowledge of multiple fields allows me to work on a project with the full scope in mind.

Experiences: Website Development (Backend, Frontend), Mobile Application, Desktop

Application

Languages: C#, C++, Java, Kotlin, Go, Javascript

Frameworks: .NET Core, .NET Framework, ReactJS, VueJS

Databases: MsSQL, Oracle Sql, Sqlite, Mongodb

IDE: Visual Studio, Android Studio, Eclipse, Visual Studio Code

Other Technologies: Oop, N-tier Architecture, Entity Framework, LINQ, REST API,

Github, Heroku

**EDUCATION** 

Management Information Systems

Anatolian University

Computer Science

September 2018 — February 2019

September 2019 — Present

Lublin University of Technology

Erasmus+ Student Exchange Programme with GPA 3.75

**Computer Engineering** 

September 2013 — February 2019

**Duzce University** 

Obtained the BS degree with GPA 2.86

**INTERESTS** 

Movie, Music, Reading, Cycling

**REFERENCES** 

References available on request

COURSE & CERTIFICATION

High-Level Android Programming with Java

ISMEK

Web Programming with .Net Core and Multitier Architecture

**ISMEK** 

March 2019 — June 2019

March 2019 — June 2019

amet Sunman 2